One God
La Elaha Ella Allah (There is no god, except the One God)
Allahu Akbar (God is great).
One God
La Elaha Ella Allah (There is no god, except the One God)
Allahu Akbar (God is great).
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
We continue to record these KHTUBAs because they are very important.
Now, I know what I'm going to talk about.
About, in fact, exactly 19 years ago, I started the research on the Quran. I put
it in the computer and you know the rest of the story. Now
after that, there was tremendous publicity for the miracle of the Quran.
We had not reached the the conclusion that is causing all kinds
of problems for the disbelievers that we shall worship God Alone, that we shall
devote ourselves to Allah Alone and that we must uphold the Quran, the
whole Quran and nothing but the Quran. Until this conclusion appeared about 1976,
there was tremendous publicity for the miracle of Quran and the putting the
Quran in the computer and it was a very popular issue. The
leaflet was distributed by the millions throughout the Muslim world
and was translated to all languages of the world, French and Japanese.
And the biblical scholars apparently became jealous and they wanted to do the
same thing. So, they did organize a very
sanctioned study at the Hebrew University in Jerusalem.
A fellow by the name of Cats put the Bible in the computer, the
Torah, the five books of Moses I guess, and what he did was to first, let's say
I'm gonna put the English but they used the original, the oldest text they could get hold of
In the beginning,... This is how the book of Genesis begins.
What they did was take every second letter.
I think they started with every seventh letter: one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. So, they took every seventh letter,
put all these letters together and tried to get meaningful words or sentences out of
them. That didn't work. So, they took every eighth letter and that didn't work.
And they kept going on until they got to some number and they found the word
Torah and they became very excited and they said God is saying that this is the
Torah and so on. They found words like: Elohim, Jerusalem
Holocaust, but these words were born from the letters that they extracted from the text -
the original text of the Bible. Last night, Larry King had a professor at the
University of California San Diego, his name was Richard Elliott Friedman.
His book is now in the market and they're making a big noise about it. The
book is entitled who wrote the Bible? and in the question and answer by
telephone, somebody asked him if he's familiar with the computer work that was done in
Israel. And I'm going to let you hear the answer.
Then I will comment from there on. Don't worry; you're going to hear it.
...computer without them to prove that it was written by different people in different times.
...that they discovered by using the computer, but the chances of the Bible being written by mortal man is only one
chance out of 1,300,000.
Sure. I'm familiar. There've been two these computer studies in recent years that supposedly prove that the Bible is all by God
or all by one person and so on.
These are non-sense. They are bogus. They are a disgrace to statistics. In simplest terms, what their system was
they counted every seventh letter of the Bible to see if it spelled out any words. It didn't
work. So, they tried every eighth letter and so on and finally on a certain number, I think, it was
every 17th letter came out every now and then spelling the word. As it happens
the word they got was Torah. Three of the four letters of Torah are the three most
common letters in the Hebrew language. And so they said so statistically, my God, how
could this have happened that it keeps out spelling Torah? It is nonsense. You
can do this with any book, the same process. You count every 14th letter of the
Bible and it will spell out Paul McCartney is dead.
Okay. This is true, I mean. As you see now, what I'm trying to tell you in this
KHUTBA is that we have the real thing. These people tried. They put the Bible in the
computer and they tried all kinds of things. Now, they're taking every 7th
letter, every 8th letter and so on. In the Quran, the discovery that came out
of this mosque, we have no choice. We cannot manipulate the data. We have two
verses initialed with the letter Q. We didn't choose Q.
The author of the Quran, Almighty Allah, chose
Q and there are two chapters initialed with Q. One is chapter 42, another
Chapter 50. You count the letter Q which is dictated on us, we did not choose it.
In chapter 42, and you have 57 Q's, 19 times 3.
You count the letter Q in chapter 50 which is half as long as 42
and you also get the same number, 57,
which is 19 times 3.
There is one chapter initialed with the letter N. We didn't choose the letter N.
There is no chance of manipulating or haphazardly looking for anything
and you count the letters in this chapter. The letter N in this chapter and
you have 133. 19 x 7. There are three chapters initialed with the
letter S, the heavy S a guttural S. Saad.
And you count this letter. There's no question about the letter Q or N or S,
they're very clear letters. And in the chapters initialed with S, you count this
letter and you'll find 152 S's which is 19 times 8.
There is no manipulation here. We have the real thing. We have proof that
every letter in Quran, every word was mathematically composed beyond human
intelligence. This is a supernatural composition. I wanted initially to
give you a report on my visit to San Diego. We had a very nice meeting last
Saturday and I find out that Apamea's aunt and
uncle were there.
I presented to them, we discussed with them the miracle of Quran and there was one
person, an objector, who came from some other camp.
And I pointed out these things to him that we have no chance of manipulating
the Quran because we did not choose the Q or the S or the N.
And I asked him to explain how come all these are consistently
multiples of 19? We have seven chapters initialed with H. M,
seven chapters. And you count these initials in the seven
chapters and you have 2147 or
19 times 113.
2147, these seven chapters are almost one tenth of the Quran and if you have one
extra H or one extra M,
this will not be a multiple of 19. It's an extremely sensitive mathematical
composition.
ALM in chapter 2, 9899 of them, you count the letter A, the letter L and letter M,
and the total is 9899. We did not choose ALM, like they skipped every seventh letter,
every eight letter, and then they took the letters out and tried to make words
out of them. Like Dr. Friedman said you can do it with any
book.
Some of the critics say you can do this with any book. But it's not true.
I tell them fine. They said you can do it to any number, not the same 19.
I say please let us see some other numbers. You know, we'd like to see
a miraculous composition of the Quran using any number. And they they haven't
shown us anything yet. 19 years until now and we challenged
them to prove any mistake here. There isn't any. Notice this is 9899,
it sounds like the price of a used car, 9899 and 99 cents. But this is a
multiple of 19.
19 times 521.
One A, one letter A, if it's added or lost becomes 9898 and that will not be
a multiple of 19. If you add one L or one M in chapter two, a huge
chapter, just one letter, lost or added and you have 9900 which is
a nice round number, but it's not a multiple of 19.
We have a chapter initialed with KHY'AS, the heavy S.
This happens to be chapter 19 and it has to do with the story of Mary and Jesus,
the virgin birth, the miracles of Jesus, things that are normally unbelievable and
this is why God is strengthening this chapter with 5 initials. And you
count them. These are distinct letters that I have in the book, the visual
presentation book, with every one of these letters marked with a star. So,
they can see for themselves. I mean, we're feeding them the miracle with a spoon.
The first book was just tables and numbers and they said how do we know
you're not lying? How do we know these numbers are correct? So, I printed the
second book for them with every letter. I said all you need to do is show me one
letter without a star, one of these letters without a star, or show
me a star under a letter that is not one of these. There are 798
of these. This is 19 times 42.
Consistently, every single one of them without exceptions, 29 chapters initialed.
And we have no choice. This KHY'AS have been in the Quran for 1400 years.
There is no chance for manipulating or playing around.
And after the conclusion came that we shall worship God Alone and uphold the
Quran Alone, you know how popular I am. They are dying to find a mistake.
It's a blessing from God that I'm not that popular.
Just received a death threat the other day. Somebody said the Saudi's gonna
assassinate you almost three days ago. That's how
popular I am. So, you can imagine how eager they are to find mistakes and you
can be sure if they find one mistake because one mistake means the whole
thing collapses and this is what I'm telling them. I said I'll forget the whole thing if you
find one mistake because God is perfect and His system is perfect.
There are other initials: ALMR,
ALMS, ALR, TSM,
TS, YS. YS is a SURA entitled YS, SURA number 36.
You count the Y and the S, in this chapter, they are 285. 19 times 15.
Strange things happen in the Quran. There is a letter Y. This letter is
questionable in many many SURAs. There are many words
like for example: یتوفکم Yatawafakum is written with a Y in the word that is
obscure Y. It's kind of a questionable Y. You do not find a single
questionable word in this SURA. They're all straightforward Y. YA SEEN. 285.
I don't know what other letters I forgot but every single one in their chapters
is a multiple of 19.
No wonder God calls this One of the Greatest Miracles.
And we are the lucky generation that witnesses this miracle.
The consequences of this Miracle certainly are fantastic and they have evolved
to the ultimate conclusion
that I've been telling you about. God is doing everything. This is the
ultimate conclusion. This ultimate conclusion explains why
the majority of believers are going to Hell.
Because there are lots of people who believe in God but they don't believe
that He's doing everything. It's a very crucial conclusion, the ultimate
conclusion.
The one that leads us to Heaven and you can understand why it is rare
that people go to Heaven. People who are going to Heaven are rare and we find this in
the Bible consistently, the Bible and the Quran. Narrow, straitened is the road to
Heaven. Wide and spacious is the road to Hell says the Bible.
The Quran says the same thing.
Tooboo Ela Allah. Repent.
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
Praise be to God. I bear witness that there is no god except the One God who is doing everything.
God is doing everything.
And some people added a few things; Lisa, the other day, was telling me she added and I
wholeheartedly submit to Him makes that another complete sentence. God is doing
everything and I wholeheartedly submit to Him. Because this ultimate conclusion
that God is doing everything sheds a whole new light
on the idea of submission to God. Because from now on you will not be an
objector. You will not be unhappy with anything.
If you're unhappy with anything, you're an objector.
If there's anything that causes unhappiness, you have to find out what it
is and eliminate it. Look for the non-Quranic situations in your life.
Eliminate them. You must live, you must be sure that
everything in your life is Quranic. Quranic means the word of God.
In the meeting in San Diego, the one fellow over there, the objecting fellow,
was saying that
out of this research came the dating for the end of the world.
The first book, the Computer Speaks, as you remember,
I said that the end of the world, God says, that the end of the world is 2280 AD,
or 1710 AH,
both of them multiples of 19. Okay. He said that this is a very dangerous thing
to say. Now, why is it dangerous, whether it is
correct or wrong? Why is it dangerous? First of all, we're not gonna live until that time.
Second of all, if it is wrong, I mean, why is it... it's a piece of information.
I must mention here that the three minimum requirements in the Quran, in SURA 2
verse 62, and also the same thing is repeated in SURA 5.
It says the minimum requirements are (1) believe in God,
(2) believe in the Hereafter (3) lead a righteous life. These are the three minimum requirements.
You'll make it to Heaven if you believe in God Alone,
believe in the Hereafter, and lead a righteous life. There is nothing about
Moses and Jesus and Muhammad. You don't have to believe in them.
There's nothing about the Quran or the Bible or the Gospel. You don't have to
believe in them. There's nothing in there about anything. There's nothing about the angels.
You believe in the angels? Of course, you believe in the angels, but it is not a
requirement. It's a piece of information. It's an additional piece of
information. There's a difference between the knowledgeable person and the ignorant
person. And all of them, if they satisfy these three requirements, they make it to
Heaven. But to believe in the angels, the messengers, the scriptures,
all these are additional pieces of information, valuable pieces of
information, and one of the valuable pieces of information is that God put in the Quran
the end of the world. So, I'm going... this KHUTBA will be devoted to this.
First of all, the Quran is God's final message to the world.
God is the only One who knows when the world will end and God wants to tell
the world about the end of the world
and when it will be. And God put it in the
in the final message to the world. So, it is not me who is saying or predicting
the end of the world. It is the All Knowledgeable, God Almighty, that is
saying in the Quran when it will end and it goes like this. In SURA 20, verse
15, God says I will not keep the end of the world hidden.
And in SURA 15, God says We have given you, O Muhammad, the seven pairs.
The seven pairs, 14.
And the letters that I showed you in the
first KHUTBA are 14, fourteen sets. So, they are, as you see, a fantastic
miracle and God is telling Muhammad what a blessing it was that God gave him
these seven pairs. Now, when the Quran was revealed, there were no numbers.
This ALM, the first verse of SURA 2, for example, you can look on them as
letters and you can also look on them as numbers.
This is 71. This was 71 at the time of revelation of
Quran. We did not have these numbers when the Quran was revealed. A is 1, L is 30, M is 40.
1+30+40. The total is 71.
You add the 14 sets of numbers, and they give you 1709, total.
So, We have given you, O, Muhammad, the verse, when you look at it carefully in view
of all the Quran, that from Muhammad to the end of the world, or from the Quran to
the end of the world, 1709 years. After you complete 1709
years, you go into 1710 After Hijra, which is a multiple of 19.
There is one flag goes up, a sign, a confirmation.
The corresponding year AD is 2280 which is also a multiple of 19. Another flag goes up.
This discovery happened in the year 1400 AH.
And it said that the end of the world will be 1709. I mean, the total
number of the letters was 1709. So, how many
years are left? How many complete years because 1710 will not be complete?
Before the end of 1710, the world will end. 309 and immediately a flag goes
up. We find in SURA 18, the people of the Cave.
God didn't tell us how many there are in the cave.
And God goes out of His way to tell us I'm not gonna tell you how many there
are in the cave. Three and people say four. Five and people say six or seven and
people say their eighth is the dog. Say God knows how many there are. So, I'm not gonna
tell you how many, but He tells us how long they lasted in the cave,
300 increased by 9. Why? This is a Quranic number and
you look the SURA and it tells you why God says, told us about the people of
the Cave. It says to remove all doubt about the end of the world.
I'm gonna say it in Arabic and the translation in English. I mean, what is more
straightforward than that? It says
وَكَذَٰلِكَ أَعْثَرْنَا عَلَيْهِمْ لِيَعْلَمُوٓا۟ أَنَّ وَعْدَ ٱللَّهِ حَقٌّۭ وَأَنَّ ٱلسَّاعَةَ لَا (18:21) رَيْبَ فِيهَآ
That the end of the world, there is no doubt about it. In other words, so this is to remove
all doubt concerning the calculations. This is connected with the end of the
world. We have given you the seven pairs is connected with the end of
the world in SURA 15.
The verse before that, before we have given you 7 pairs, God says that God is the
Omniscient who knows, the Creator, the Omniscient, who knows everything
and knows when the world will end.
(15:85) وَإِنَّ ٱلسَّاعَةَ لَـَٔاتِيَةٌۭ ۖ فَٱصْفَحِ ٱلصَّفْحَ ٱلْجَمِيلَ
(15:86) إِنَّ رَبَّكَ هُوَ ٱلْخَلَّـٰقُ ٱلْعَلِيمُ
That your Lord is the Creator, the Omniscient who
knows when it will end. We have given you seven pairs
and the great Quran. So, all these signs together tell us that there is no doubt.
But it is a piece of information, it is not required
to go to Heaven. The minimum requirements are (1) believe in
God (2) believe in the Hereafter (3) lead a righteous life under any name. If you're
a Buddhist or Hindu or Christian or Jewish or Muslim, under any name, if you worship
God Alone, the Creator of the universe and believe in the Hereafter, Heaven
And Hell, Resurrection after death, and lead a righteous life. You can't just
believe in God and the Hereafter and be a nasty, bad person, liar, cheat and all that.
You have to lead a righteous life. So, these three minimum requirements will
lead you to Heaven. Belief in the messengers, Muhammad, Jesus, Moses is not
required, the angels is not required. Believing in the scriptures is not required.
We don't see it in the.. Believing that the world will end in 1710 or 2280 is not
required, but it is a valuable piece of information as valuable as knowing
that there are angels and jinns and messengers
and scriptures.
Aqem Al-Salat.